# Damjan Pjević,

a student at the School of Economics and Business

## PERSONAL STATEMENT

An ambitious, reliable and open-minded individual with a great passion in tech and business. With a Bachelors in Multimedia Engineering focused on Digital Communication, I am in pursuit of my master's degree in Business Informatics at the School of Economics and Business in Ljubljana. Experienced with working with the clients, public speaking and working in a team and with a working history in the fields of the computer software industry, event organisation, digital media and marketing.

### **SKILLS**

IT Website management, mobile

application development, basics

in telecommuniations.

Programming Java, JavaScript, Python, HTML &

CSS, WordPress.

Marketing & PR Content creation, verbal

communication, promotional events.

Languages Slovenian C2, English C2, Serbian

B2, German B1, Russian A1.

## **EXPERIENCES**

## Epicoro [2020–now]

## Wordpress developer

- Building basic and intermediate websites using Elementor and Wordpress for various local companies.
- Restructuring processes using Click-Up and Airtable.
- Helping out with photography, video editing and live streaming.

## Website manager & Content creator

Value Add Games [2019–2020]

- Helped in marketing with the launch
- of their most successful product.
- Re-established the online shop.
- Maintained the website and the online shop.

### **Technical Assistant**

Chamber of Commerce and Industry of Slovenia [2019 – 2020]

- Independently overseeing technical aspect and providing support for online events with around 10 speakers and more than 100 participants carried out in English or Slovenian.
- Recorded and edited over 50 videos (presentations and reportages) for various events.

Contact damjan@pjevic.com +386 40 933 622 Online presence www.pjevic.com linkedin.com/in/pjevic

### **EDUCATION**

2020–2022 Business Informatics – Masters.
School of Economics and Business,

University of Ljubljana, Slovenia

2015–2019 Multimedia Engineering – Bachelors.
Faculty of Electrical Engineering,
University of Ljubljana, Slovenia

Hochschule für Kunst Bremen, Germany (Erasmus Exchange 2017)

## Selected class projects

- Extension of the Pan-European Mobile Emergency Application with extended reality.
- Using Android SDK created and designed a translation app for one of the Slovene dialects.

#### **Extracurriculars:**

[2019] Took part in the BEST Summer

Course in Wroclaw, Poland that focuses on company management and how technology and good marketing strategy can embrace its success.

[2016–2019] Took part in various promotional

events of the faculty.

[2012–2015] Took part in three different YouthPass

exchanges all focused on international

Peer-to-Peer communication.

[2011–2015] High School Debate club.

### **AWARDS**

[2017] Reached top 20 out of 350 global

teams in OnePlus Student Marketing

Challenge.

[2016] Regional winners in global competition

OSCE.

Peer to Peer: Challenging Extremism by a successfully developed and pitched tool

for challenging violent extremism.



# Damjan Pjević,

a student at the School of Economics and Business

Contact damjan@pjevic.com +386 40 933 622 Online presence www.pjevic.com linkedin.com/in/pjevic

### PERSONAL STATEMENT

An ambitious, reliable and open-minded individual with a great passion in tech and business. With a Bachelors in Multimedia Engineering focused on Digital Communication, I am in pursuit of my master's degree in Business Informatics at the School of Economics and Business in Ljubljana. Experienced with working with the clients, public speaking and working in a team and with a working history in the fields of the computer software industry, event organisation, digital media and marketing.

#### **EDUCATION**

2020 – 2022 Business Informatics – Masters.
School of Economics and Business,
University of Ljubljana, Slovenia

2015 – 2019 Multimedia Engineering – Bachelors.

Average grade: 9.0 Faculty of Electrical Engineering, University of Ljubljana, Slovenia

Hochschule für Kunst Bremen, Germany (Erasmus Exchange 2017)

### **SKILLS**

Marketing & PR Content creation, verbal communication, promotional events.
 IT Website management, mobile application development, basics in telecommunications.
 Languages Slovenian C2, English C2, Serbian B2, German B1, Russian A1.

### Selected class projects

- Extension of the Pan-European Mobile Emergency Application with extended reality.
- Using Android SDK created and designed a translation app for one of the Slovene dialects.

### **EXPERIENCES**

Value Add Games

2019 - Now

## Website manager & Content creator

- Helped in marketing with the launch of their most successful product.
- Re-established the online shop.
- Maintained the website and the online shop.

Chamber of Commerce and Industry of Slovenia 2019 – Now **Technical Assistant** 

- Independently overseeing technical aspect and providing support for online events with around 10 speakers and more than 100 participants carried out in English or Slovenian.
- Recorded and edited over 50 videos (presentations and reportages) for various events.

### Extracurriculars

Took part in the BEST Summer Course in Wroclaw, Poland that focuses on company management and how technology and good marketing strategy can embrace its success.

[2016 – 2019] Took part in various promotional events of

the faculty.

[2012 – 2015] Took part in three different YouthPass

exchanges all focused on international

Peer-to-Peer communication.

[2011 – 2015] High School Debate club.

## EESTEC - LC Ljubljana

2015 - 2016

# Member & Multimedia coordinator

- As one of the Coordinators, success fully managed the PR group for EESTEC Competition for Android 2015 and reached out to more students than any year before.
- Took part in a week-long seminar in Istanbul, Turkey focused on Marketing and Multimedia.

### **AWARDS**

[2019]

[2017] Reached top 20 out of 350 global teams in OnePlus Student Marketing

Challenge.

[2016] Regional winners in global competition

OSCE

Peer to Peer: Challenging Extremism by a successfully developed and pitched tool for challenging violent extremism.